bestyummyrecipes.com 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - All food Recipes

Privacy Policy for the Website http://www.allfood.recipes

The privacy of our visitors is important to us.

We recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what forms of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit our website, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

Web Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in the sites log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as commenting.

DoubleClick DART Cookies

We may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (“interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about buying a new car, you may see car advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about knitting). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

Third Party Advertisements

We may also use third party advertisements to support our website such as Google AdSense, Chitika, Clickbank, Kontera, Infolinks, LinkWords… Some of these advertisers may use cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes, for example showing London Restaurant ads to someone in London or showing relevant ads based on sites you have recently visited for example showing car ads to someone who visits car relevant websites.

You can disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as commenting.

 _We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:  [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://recipes.yumm.netdna-cdn.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/05/opt_out.asp)_

End of Privacy Policy for the Website http://www.allfood.recipes/
